<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>benforce.io</title>
    <description>Serverless blogging at its finest.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Forwarding Tenvis security camera emails to S3 (with notifications!)</title>
        <description>
          
          So you just got that brand new security cam to keep you safe at night. But you skimped out a bit and bought the cheap Tenvis IPCam on Amazon to save a few bucks. Very soon after setup you get annoyed that the app doesn’t run in the background of...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017-08-03-connecting-tenvis-cam-to-s3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017-08-03-connecting-tenvis-cam-to-s3/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Receiving .io certificate confirmation emails with Amazon SES</title>
        <description>
          
          So you just registered one of those super trendy .io domains that all the cool kids have these days. You’re a boss because you paid $40 instead of $13 for the .com you wanted but was already taken. Now its time to set up your static site in S3 on...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017-07-26-receiving-io-certificate-validation-email/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017-07-26-receiving-io-certificate-validation-email/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using Hyper-V for an isolated VPN torrent box</title>
        <description>
          
          I’ve been searching a long time now for the perfect VPN Torrent box and have ultimately not be satisfied with a lot of the solutions. They all fail to meet one or more of my requirements. The most common suggested solution is using an internet kill switch from a VPN...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016-12-16-hyperv-for-isolated-vpn-torrent/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016-12-16-hyperv-for-isolated-vpn-torrent/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus day is a racist and stupid holiday</title>
        <description>
          
          I’ve decided this year from here forward, I will refuse to acknowledge the second Monday of October as ‘Christopher Columbus’ day. I encourage everybody to read a little bit about it. Think about it. We are supposed to celebrate some guy that “discovered” America, a place where people already lived!?...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016-10-11-Columbus-Day-is-a-Racist-and-Stupid-Holiday/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016-10-11-Columbus-Day-is-a-Racist-and-Stupid-Holiday/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
